<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speed of Trust on FishLasers</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/tags/speed-of-trust/</link><description>Recent content in Speed of Trust on FishLasers</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:58:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fishlasers.co.uk/tags/speed-of-trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/bio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/bio/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Both.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>SPEED OF TRUST&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ROSIE MCLEAN&lt;/p>
&lt;p>@ FUSION ARTS&lt;/p>
&lt;p>95 GLOUCESTER GREEN&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Fri 24TH NOVEMBER- fri 8TH DECEMBER&lt;/p>
&lt;p>WEDNESDAY - SUNDAY 11am-6pm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.rosiemclean.com">www.rosiemclean.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The materiality and associations of glass invite us to attend to the plasticity of our attentions and perceptions, and consider how they might be different. Glass can be melted and reformed indefinitely. We associate it largely with devices that help us “see”, such as windows or lenses, and as a vessel for liquids. It does itself liquify to a viscous syrup at around 1700 degrees celsius.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Counting on Light Relief</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/10/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Counting%20on%20light%20relief.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This work is located in the centre of the gallery, facing the entrance. A decorators dust sheet hangs vertically down from a wooden 1 by 2 inch baton, and measures about 2 metres high by 1.7 metres across. Hanging from another baton above this is a textural mesh depicting an abstract dreamscape comprised of different applications of beadwork interspersed with repurposed textiles, crocheted chain and natural materials. On the right side naive style beaded webs in red hang. Other sections evoke sunsets, flames, clouds and liquid.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 1</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/1/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2014.49.06.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>The first piece, as you walk through the entrance, is straight ahead of you, suspended from the ceiling on see through wire. It has an overall form resembling seaweed, and is made up of melted glass beads in dark reds and golden yellows, and uncolored glass embedded with white ash and black embers. It moves lightly as you walk past it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 8</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/8/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/s8.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>On a low plinth on the right hand wall as you enter the gallery is this asymetrical pyramid shaped piece of wood, pale pine in colour, around 20 x 20cm. It is bound with red and pink lengths of beaded wire. The wood has been burned in places and the beads melted and fused together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 9</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/9/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/s9.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>On a low plinth on the right hand wall as you enter the gallery is this chunk of oak bark, approx 15 by 10 cm, dark brown in colour with a rough and gnarled texture. It is bound with dark blue and gold beads on lengths of wire. The bark has been burned in places and the beads melted and fused together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Voice Form 1</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf1/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Voice%20Form%201.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>An abstract charcoal drawing on an A3 piece of paper, positioned landscape, ripped at the top where it has been torn from a sketchbook. The form sits centre left, with one fluid line leading from the middle to the bottom right. A smoke like three leaf clover shape leads off this towards top right corner. Underneath that a jagged line, which alternates between thick, thin, bold and soft, trails off the bottom left of the page. In the middle three large wavy horizontal lines in step formation, and a pillar shaped cloud of dots and lines like a constellation on the far left.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Voice Form 2</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf2/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Voice%20Form%202.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>An abstract charcoal drawing on an A3 piece of paper, positioned landscape, ripped at the top where it has been torn from a sketchbook. The form rests on the upper half of the page. Twin dominant, dark lines proceed across the form, merging and once again forking on the right. Several softer lines in various thicknesses coil up from the left side, undulating through and above the dominant lines. A thick, medium bold, tightly coiled line attaches to the bottom right of the central lines, un-coiling at the ends.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Voice Form 3</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/vf3/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Voice%20Form%203.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>An abstract charcoal drawing on an A3 piece of paper, positioned landscape, ripped at the top where it has been torn from a sketchbook. This form fills most of the page.
A dark section filling most of the bottom left quadrant forms scratchy overlapping waves trailing towards the middle. Softer marks spill upwards and right from this, filling the page with spirals, wavy lines and loops.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 2</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/2/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2014.45.24.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This piece is a multimedia amorphous sculpture in a form resembling a cranial shape.
It&amp;rsquo;s comprised of uncolored glass in ribbon-like forms with embedded white ash and black embers, moving into red and orange beads strung on a wire frame, and blue and red ribbon-like glass frozen as if in molten state.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 3</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/3/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2015.05.14.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>In the middle of the room is an amorphous mixed media piece, with overall form similar to an elongated animal skull. It&amp;rsquo;s lit by a small white light adjacent to it. It&amp;rsquo;s primarily made up of beadwork in fire colours of red, orange and gold, woven with thick ribbon-like pieces of uncoloured ochre glass, some with white ash and black embers from the fire embedded in them. It&amp;rsquo;s the nose of the piece, lighter pink beads and wire work is visible.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 4</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/4/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2015.36.19.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>This piece is a large multimedia sculpture with the overall form reminiscent of the head of a magical scaled creature. It&amp;rsquo;s lit from inside of the head. This piece comprises small golden beads, a part of an elongated sculpture leading into a mix of green, gold and blue bead work interlaced with large pieces of golden green and blue glass forms, some still with visible signs of being part in the past recycled bottles. The nose of the piece has opaque white glass frosted with white ash from the fire and small specks of charcoal in shades of green and blue glass, as if frozen in a molten state.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 5</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/5/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2015.47.34.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>In the far corner from the entrance, suspended by multiple invisible strings hangs a multimedia sculpture in a form resembling a large crystal. It is uplit casting two different shadows, cuboid in shape, one larger than the other. The sculpture is predominantly made up of strings of gold, red and black beadwork and chunks of mostly uncoloured glass woven with ribbon-like pieces of green and blue glass, or frozen as if in molten state.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 6</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/6/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/s6.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>On a low plinth at the back of the gallery is this spidery, round, and fairly flat blue and gold melted glass form, largely composed of interlocking lengths of melted beads on wire. It has been embellished latterly with un-melted seed and glass beads which sparkle. Ash and charcoal are visible on the inside.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass 7</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/7/</guid><description>&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/s7.m4a" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>On a low plinth at the back of the gallery is this abstract, hollow glass form with red melted lengths of beads, like veins, connecting slabs of bottle green, clear and blue glass. In the gaps it has been re-beaded in purple and petrol seed beads and silver beads which sparkle. Ash and charcoal are visible on the inside.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fire Pit</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/fireinglass/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/fireinglass/</guid><description>&lt;p>Audio description for the Fire Pit:&lt;/p>
&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/WhatsApp%20Audio%202023-11-24%20at%2015.26.46.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>Recording of Assia&amp;rsquo;s singing:&lt;/p>
&lt;figure >
 &lt;audio controls preload="metadata">
 &lt;source src="https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/audio/Fire%20Pit%202.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
 &lt;/audio>
 
 &lt;/figure>
&lt;p>As you are by the fire pit, through the headphones you will hear an ethereal voice singing in an alto register, a mid-high vocal range, without any words.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>