<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Speed Of Trust on FishLasers</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/tags/speed-of-trust/</link><description>Recent content in Speed Of Trust on FishLasers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:58:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fishlasers.co.uk/tags/speed-of-trust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/bio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/bio/</guid><description>SPEED OF TRUST
ROSIE MCLEAN
@ FUSION ARTS
95 GLOUCESTER GREEN
Fri 24TH NOVEMBER- fri 8TH DECEMBER
WEDNESDAY - SUNDAY 11am-6pm
www.rosiemclean.com
The materiality and associations of glass invite us to attend to the plasticity of our attentions and perceptions, and consider how they might be different. Glass can be melted and reformed indefinitely. We associate it largely with devices that help us “see”, such as windows or lenses, and as a vessel for liquids.</description></item><item><title>Counting on Light Relief</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/10/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Speed of Trust 1</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/1/</guid><description>The first piece, as you walk through the entrance, is straight ahead of you, suspended from the ceiling on see through wire. It has an overall form resembling seaweed, and is made up of melted glass beads in dark reds and golden yellows, and uncolored glass embedded with white ash and black embers. It moves lightly as you walk past it.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Trust 2</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/2/</guid><description>This piece is a multimedia amorphous sculpture in a form resembling a cranial shape. It&amp;rsquo;s comprised of uncolored glass in ribbon-like forms with embedded white ash and black embers, moving into red and orange beads strung on a wire frame, and blue and red ribbon-like glass frozen as if in molten state.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Trust 3</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/3/</guid><description>In the middle of the room is an amorphous mixed media piece, with overall form similar to an elongated animal skull. It&amp;rsquo;s lit by a small white light adjacent to it. It&amp;rsquo;s primarily made up of beadwork in fire colours of red, orange and gold, woven with thick ribbon-like pieces of uncoloured ochre glass, some with white ash and black embers from the fire embedded in them. It&amp;rsquo;s the nose of the piece, lighter pink beads and wire work is visible.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Trust 4</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/4/</guid><description>This piece is a large multimedia sculpture with the overall form reminiscent of the head of a magical scaled creature. It&amp;rsquo;s lit from inside of the head. This piece comprises small golden beads, a part of an elongated sculpture leading into a mix of green, gold and blue bead work interlaced with large pieces of golden green and blue glass forms, some still with visible signs of being part in the past recycled bottles.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Trust 5</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/5/</guid><description>In the far corner from the entrance, suspended by multiple invisible strings hangs a multimedia sculpture in a form resembling a large crystal. It is uplit casting two different shadows, cuboid in shape, one larger than the other. The sculpture is predominantly made up of strings of gold, red and black beadwork and chunks of mostly uncoloured glass woven with ribbon-like pieces of green and blue glass, or frozen as if in molten state.</description></item><item><title>Fire in Glass</title><link>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/fireinglass/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:58:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fishlasers.co.uk/speedoftrust/fireinglass/</guid><description>Audio description for the Fire Pit:
Recording of Assia&amp;rsquo;s singing:
As you are by the fire pit, through the headphones you will hear an ethereal voice singing in an alto register, a mid-high vocal range, without any words.
The sound has an echo as if recorded in a cave or cathedral.
The notes start low then soar higher, then play between low and high notes before soaring higher and then higher again.</description></item></channel></rss>